hijordan.com 2011-08-19

# Privacy Notice : Air Jordan Shoes, Michael Jordan Shoes

HiJordan believes in keeping your confidential information confidential. We do not sell any information about our users on the individual customer level.

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make any material changes in the way we collect, use, and/or share your personal information, we will notify you by sending you an email at the last email address that you provided us, and/or by prominently posting notice of the changes on the website covered by this Privacy Policy. Any material changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective upon the earlier of thirty (30) calendar days following our transmittal of an email notice to you or thirty (30) calendar days following our posting of the notice of changes on the website covered by the Privacy Policy.

Please note that, at all times, you are responsible for updating your personal information to provide us your current email address. In the event that the last email address that you have provided us is not valid, or for any other reason is not capable of delivering to you the notice described above, our transmittal of the email containing such notice will nevertheless constitute effective notice of the changes described in the notice.

In any event, changes to this Privacy Policy may affect our use of personal information that you provided us prior to our notification to you of the changes. If you do not wish to permit changes in our use of your information, you must notify us prior to the effective date of the changes that you wish to deactivate your account with us.
